Mss.B.H357.p
American Philosophical Society
- I. Correspondence
  - Strasenburgh, R J
  - Strassman, Paul
  - Straus, Friedrich
  - Straus, Lionel F Jr.
  - Strauss, Florence
  - Strauss, Frederich
  - Strauss, Frederick
  - Strawn, Nellie Peeler
  - Streblich, J
  - Strecker, Edward A
  - Street, Julian
  - Strickland, Hilda
  - Strong, J H
  - Strong, R W
  - Strong, Richard P
  - Strong, William J H
  - Strother, Bryant L
  - Strothman, L B
  - Stuart, Allan
  - Stuart, Grace
  - Stuart, Kathleen M
  - Stump & Walter Co.
  - Stupakoff Ceramic & Mfg. Co.
  - Sturtevant, Charles N
  - Sugar Beet Products Co.
  - Suit, Dewey L
  - Sullivan & Cromwell
  - Sullivan, Henry A.
  - Sullivan, Loretto
  - Sullivan, Margaret A
  - Summers, Cora M
  - Summers, L E
  - Sumner, Elizabeth Heizer
  - Sumner, G Lynn
  - Sundwall, Charlotte M
  - Sun-Yat-Sen
  - Super Health Aluminum Co., Ltd
  - Supervision Publishing Co.
  - Surety Savings and Loan Association
  - Surrey Associates
  - Surrey Graphic
  - Sussman, Stephen L
  - Suter, Fred W
  - Sutterby, James H
  - Sutton, C O
  - Sutton, Catherine
  - Sutton, Richard, Jr.
  - Svaty, Vera
  - Swan, Mabel
  - Sweet, W C
  - Sweetser, Arthur
  - Swellengrebel, N H
  - Swenk, Robert G
  - Swenson, Ida W
  - Swets & Zeitlinger
  - Swift & Company
  - Switzerland, Legation of
  - Sykes, Mrs.
  - Symonds, G R B
  - Syrcher, E Victor
  - Syroid, Helen
  - Szechenyi, Gladys
  - Tabori, Cornelius
  - Taft, James R
  - Taft, William Howard
  - Taintor, Charles
  - Talley, Ruth M
  - Tan, Cesarea
  - Tanny, M Richard
  - Tansey, Katherine
  - Tapp, E A
  - Tappan Stove Co.
  - Tarbert, Minnie
  - Tate, E Mallory
  - Taxy, Sol
  - Tay, S W
  - Taylor, Bruce
  - Taylor, Frederic W
  - Taylor, Helen A
  - Taylor, J
  - Taylor, J Richard
  - Taylor, Martin
  - Taylor, Myra Rafton
  - Taylor, Nancy
  - Taylor, Orla B
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association of America
  - Teitz, John W
  - Teitz, William
  - Teleky, Ludwig
  - Temple University
  - Tennessee Aircraft Inc.
  - Tennessee Coal Iron & Railroad Co.
  - Tennessee Eastman Corp.
  - Tennessee Regional Industrial Health Conference Nashville
  - Tennessee Taxpayers Association, Inc.
  - Tennessee. Department of Public Health
  - Terris, Milton
  - Terry, T A
  - Tether, Russell W
  - Texas Company
  - Texas. Department of Health
  - Texas. State Tuberculosis Sanitorium
  - Textile Machine Works
  - Thau, William
  - The American Society for the Control of Cancer, Inc.
  - The Brooklyn Museum
  - The John & Mary R. Markle Foundation
  - The Medical Bureau
  - The Netherlands. Batavia. Burgerlijken Geneeskundigen Dienst
  - The Star
  - The Survey
  - The Woods Schools
  - Thedeman, W L
  - Thermoid Co.
  - Think Magazine
  - Thom, Dorothy
  - Thoma, Kittner
  - Thomas Jefferson Inn
  - Thomas, Amelia
  - Thomas, Elizabeth D
  - Thomas, H B
  - Thomas, Jean Grant
  - Thomas, Lowell
  - Thomas, Wilbur K
  - Thompkins, Wyntha A
  - Thompson, A M
  - Thompson, Arthur S
  - Thompson, J D
  - Thompson, L W
  - Thompson, Lydia
  - Thompson, Mrs. A
  - Thorn, Ernest M
  - Thorne, J I
  - Thorne, Samuel
  - Thornton, E Q
  - Three Hills
  - Thurmond, Ray G
  - Thurston, Lloyd
  - Tiant, Fransicso
  - Ticonium
  - Tidningen, Idun
  - Tillman, Nelson W
  - Time
  - Tirtoff-Romanoff, Prince Vladimr
  - Titus, Alice F
  - Tobias, Charles H
  - Toby & Kirk
  - Today's Health
  - Todd Shipyard Corp.
  - Todd, Eveleth R
  - Todd, Mrs. C S
  - Todd, Richard N
  - Todhunter, E Neige
  - Toledo Edison Co.
  - Tomacelli, La Contessa Maria Claudia
  - Tonopah Mining Co. of Nevada
  - Tool Steel Gear and Pinion Co.
  - Topics Publishing Co., Inc.
  - Torbert, John Keith
  - Tortorella, Mary
  - Towill, Pamela
  - Town Hall Series, Inc.
  - Towne, Vincent
  - Towns, Charles B
  - Townsend, C S
  - Townsend, Henry S
  - Townsend, J G
  - Townsend, Mrs. E M
  - Towse, Anna B
  - Towse, Irma B
  - Tracy, W Ward
  - Traina, Sal
  - Tranor, Arthur B
  - Transradio Press Service, Inc.
  - Trask, Caroline B
  - Traubee Products, Inc.
  - Trautz, F M
  - Travelers Health Institutes
  - Travis, Maury M
  - Treanor, Anne
  - Treat, Olive G
  - Tregoe, Benjamin D
  - Tregoe, Marianne
  - Trench and Marine Pump Co.
  - Tresk, Benjamin H
  - Trianon Palace Hotel
  - Trick, Mrs. J
  - Trion Facts
  - Triple Check Laboratories, Inc.
  - Troillet, J
  - Tropical Disease Center
  - Tropical Disease Research Laboratories
  - Trotter, Frederick
  - True, Peggy
  - Truman, A M T
  - Trumbull, Harriet E
  - Trunecek, Joseph
  - Tsaleridis, Constantine
  - Tschirky, Oscar
  - Tuberculosis and Health Society, Harrisburg and Dauphin County, Pa.
  - Tucker, Charles E
  - Tucker, Mary Leone
  - Tucker, R P
  - Tugi, Premier of Tonga
  - Tully, Emily Cole (Mrs. James)
  - Turnbull, A C
  - Turnbull, William G
  - Turner, C E
  - Turner, Charlotte N
  - Turner, F P
  - Turner, Hugh
  - Turner, Rose V
  - Tuthill, Howard S
  - Tuxedo Club
  - Tyler, O K
  - Tyson, Bruno
  - U S Post Office - New York City
  - U. S. Department of Commerce
  - U.S. Army
  - U.S. Army Map Service
  - U.S. Bureau of the Budget
  - U.S. Civil Service Commission
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture
  - U.S. Department of State
  - U.S. Department of the Interior
  - U.S. Government Office of Strategic Services
  - U.S. Internal Revenue
  - U.S. Office of Indian Affairs
  - U.S. Postmaster
  - U.S. Public Health Service
  - U.S. Selective Service System. Veterans Personnel Division
  - U.S. Senate
  - U.S. Senate. Committee on Manufactures
  - U.S. War Dept.
  - U.S. War Food Administration
  - U.S. War Manpower Commission
  - U.S. War Production Board
  - U.S. War Relocation Authority
  - U.S. War Shipping Administration
  - Uchitil, Auguste
  - Uganda Protectorate Medical Department
  - Uganda. Director of Medical Service
  - Uhlemann, William R
  - Union Boiler and Mfg. Co.
  - Union Carbide and Carbon Corp.
  - Union League of Philadelphia.
  - Union of South Africa
  - Union of South Africa. Department of Public Health
  - United Council for Civilian Relief in China
  - United Fruit Company
  - United Hospital Campaign
  - United Hospital Fund of New York
  - United Merchants and Manufacturers
  - United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration
  - United Office and Professional Workers of America
  - United Service to China, Inc.
  - United States Hoffman Machinery Co.
  - United States Junior Chamber of Commerce
  - United States Leather Co.
  - United States Military Academy
  - United States Navy Department
  - United States News
  - United States Office for Emergency Management
  - United States Rubber Co.
  - United States Rubber Plantations, Inc.
  - United States Steel Corp.
  - United States Tobacco Co.
  - United States Vitamin Corp.
  - United States. Dept. of Labor
  - United States. Government Printing Office
  - United States. Treasury Department
  - Universal Atlas Cement Co.
  - University Club
  - Updegraff, Helen
  - Upson, M M
  - Upson, Walter Lyman
  - Upton, J Duane
  - Upton, Louis
  - Urbach, Erick
  - Ussher, Clarence D
  - USV Pharmaceutical Corporation
  - Utah Savings & Loan Association
  - Utilities & Industries Corporation
  - Utt, Marjorie E
  - Uylangoo, Cesar
  - Vaccination
  - Vahlteich, H W
  - Valeria Home
  - Valle, Roy del
  - Valley View Inn
  - Valvoline Pipe Lines
  - Van Cleve, Mildred
  - Van Dam, Mordecai and Co., Inc.
  - Van Doren, Irita
  - Van Driel, B M
  - Van Dusen, D
  - Van Gilder, John S
  - Van Hoesen, H M
  - Van Loon, J C
  - Van Meter, W R
  - Van Ness, Thelma J
  - Vance, Helen
  - Vance, J F
  - Vander Woude, Mary (Mrs. R)
  - Vanderlip, Narcissa Cox
  - Vanderwall, Norman
  - Vaschak, Mathilda R
  - Vassar Company
  - Vassiliou, Ileana
  - Vaughan, Henry F
  - Veasey, Clarence A
  - Vecchione, Philomena
  - Veeder-Root, Inc.
  - Velasco, Felix
  - Venetsanos, George
  - Vera, Miguel
  - Vercouteren, Helen
  - Vergeer, Teunis
  - Vermont, Department of Public Health
  - Vezina, Elie
  - Victor Heiser Tennis Club
  - Victory Loan Campaign
  - Viet, Rose
  - Viking Press
  - Villamin, Vincente
  - Villard, Oswald Garrison
  - Vilter Mfg. Co.
  - Vincent, George E
  - Virginia. Arlington County Health Department
  - Visanska, B
  - Vischer, Peter
  - Visiting Nurse Association
  - Vital Foods Corp.
  - Vitality Records, Inc.
  - Vitamin-Quota
  - Vitex Laboratories, Inc.
  - Vit-O-Scope
  - Vivisection
  - Vondermuhll, George A
  - Vuehinich, Vuk
  - Wade, H Windsor
  - Wagner, Anna L
  - Wagner, Augst H
  - Wagner, Lillian C
  - Wagner, Marcel E
  - Wagner-Murray-Dingell Bill
  - Wahl, Edward F
  - Waine, Edith (Mrs. Hans)
  - Waine, Hans
  - Waldeck, Herman
  - Waldes-Kohinoor, Inc.
  - Waldron, Rosalind
  - Walker, H E
  - Walker, Harold O
  - Walker, John C
  - Walker, S A
  - Wallace and Tierman
  - Wallace, Mary R
  - Wallace, Norman E
  - Wallace, Regina
  - Walls, Milton G
  - Walls, Thomas
  - Walradt, F S
  - Walsh, David I
  - Walsh, Verne
  - Walsh, William Henry
  - Walters, Helen M
  - Walters, Kathleen
  - Wampler, Fred J
  - Wamsutta Mills
  - Wanamaker, Olin D
  - Wander Company
  - Ward, E St. John
  - Ward, Mr. & Mrs.
  - Ward, S C
  - Wardwell,Allen
  - Warner & Swasey Co.
  - Warner Brothers Pictures, Incorporated
  - Warner, Frank D
  - Warner, H D
  - Warner, Mrs. H D
  - Warner, Virginia
  - Warren, AL--Health Observations re Dr. Hsu
  - Warren, C L
  - Warren, Pa. Register of Deeds
  - Warshaw, Leon J
  - Washburn, Gloria
  - Washington State Nutrition Committee
  - Waters, Robert S
  - Waters, Somerset R
  - Watkins, J.R., co.
  - Watson, Cassius H
  - Watson, Nancy (Mrs. Walter S)
  - Watt, A.P., & Son
  - Watt, Alfred R
  - Watt, Eileen
  - Watt, T B
  - Watt,M H
  - Watterson, John A
  - Waukegan (ILL.) News
  - Waxler, Shirley
  - Waxman, Percy
  - Wayne County (Mich.) Medical Society
  - Wayne University
  - Wayson, N E
  - Weatherbe, W A
  - Weaver, Anderson
  - Weaver, Eunice C
  - Webb, J R D
  - Weber, E W
  - Weber, H Frederic
  - Weber, Mary Evalena
  - Weber, Pearl
  - Webster, F W
  - Webster, Norman C
  - Webster, Warren Co.
  - Webster-Brinkley Co.
  - Weidberg, Joseph m
  - Weigle, W Harold
  - Weimer, Vivian L
  - Weisner, Margaret M
  - Weiss, Morton D
  - Weissburger, Jose
  - Weissenstein, Josef
  - Welch, William Henry
  - Welkor, Marian
  - Wellington Hotel
  - Wellman, S. K., Co.
  - Wells, Elizabeth D (Mrs. Philip V.)
  - Welsh, Charles J
  - Wendell, Arthur R
  - Wendell, Barrett
  - Wendt, Charles W
  - Wenman, Mrs. J
  - Wentworth, Jack
  - Werner, Eliza Anne
  - Wertheim Fellowship Scholarship
  - Wertheim, Edward L
  - West Disinfecting Co.
  - West Virginia Manufacturers Association
  - West Virginia. State Health Department
  - Western-Lee First Aid Office
  - Westinghouse Electric Corp.
  - Weysfield, Catherine Wally
  - Whalen, Frank
  - Whalen, Grover
  - Wheat Flour Institute
  - Wheaton, James A
  - Wheeler, E V
  - Wheeler, Eileen
  - Wheelock, Eleanor
  - Wheelock, Thomas
  - Whipple, Carolyn
  - Whitaker, Jeanne
  - Whitbeck, H J
  - White House Company
  - White, E H
  - White, E L
  - White, Fay
  - White, J H
  - White, Jean Martin
  - White, John R
  - White, Mrs. W M
  - White, Paul Dudley
  - White, S Marx
  - White, W Harry H
  - White, William Allen
  - Whitestone, Betsey T
  - Whitlow, Lula Nell
  - Whitney, L Holland
  - Whitridge, Arnold
  - Whittaker, Alfred H
  - Whittaker, B A
  - Whittemore, Grace Conner
  - Whittenberg, MRS. H E
  - Who (Magazine)
  - Who's Who
  - Who's who in America
  - Who's who in the east
  - Wickenden, Homer
  - Wiedmann, H E
  - Wiese, B F
  - Wigglesworth, Richard B
  - Wild, James Heiser
  - Wilder, Richard E
  - Wilder, Russell M
  - Wilhite, Gertrude
  - Wilkinson, Elizabeth
  - Willey, Malcolm M
  - Williams Bakery Co.
  - Williams Mfg. Co.
  - Williams, Annie Laurie
  - Williams, Ben Ames
  - Williams, Bernard T
  - Williams, C H
  - Williams, Dorothy
  - Williams, H
  - Williams, Helen
  - Williams, Herbert U
  - Williams, J. H. & Co.
  - Williams, John H
  - Williams, John K
  - Williams, L B
  - Williams, Mary Hotchkins (Mrs. Sydney M)
  - Williams, Mildred C
  - Williams, Peggy
  - Williams, Robert
  - Williams, Robert B
  - Williams, Roger W
  - Williams, Tom A
  - Williams,W C
  - Williamson, Mrs. C
  - Williamsport (Pa.) Community Trade Association
  - Willis, Florence
  - Willis, H Hastings
  - Willits, Nita
  - Wills, Angela G
  - Wilson, Adelaide
  - Wilson, Al, Company
  - Wilson, Alfred M
  - Wilson, Barry A
  - Wilson, Bessie
  - Wilson, H. W. Co.
  - Wilson, Harold G
  - Wilson, Howard
  - Wilson, Isabelle
  - Wilson, Leda Margaret
  - Wilson, Marion E
  - Wilson, R Manton
  - Wilson, Virginia E
  - Wilson, William G
  - Windsor, Duke of
  - Wines, George M
  - Winfield, Sydney J
  - Winn, J N Jr.
  - Winser, Ethel Reid
  - Winship, Blanton
  - Winslow, C E A
  - Winter, James A
  - Winterbottom, William
  - Winterhalter, Harold
  - Wirt, S Edgar
  - Wisconsin Dietetic Association
  - Wisconsin. State Board of Health
  - Wise, Mrs. S F
  - Wise, S P III
  - Wise, Walter D
  - Wise, Wesley W
  - Wiseman, Frederick A
  - Witheby, (Mrs. FRH)
  - Witlock, Luke
  - Wittmer, John J
  - Witzig, Marion
  - Woellner, Robert C
  - Wohlgemuth, Margaret C
  - Woke, Paul A
  - Wolcott, Harold C
  - Wolf, B J
  - Wolf, Stanley J
  - Wolfe, Louis A
  - Wolfe, Mary H
  - Wolferz, Ellen
  - Wolff, Ed
  - Wolff, Frederico
  - Wolfson, Marguerite
  - Wolinski, Pauline
  - Wolpaw, Ralph
  - Woman's Forum, Litchfield, Conn.
  - Woman's Medical College of Pennsylvania.
  - Women in Industry
  - Women's Advertising Club of Chicago
  - Womens National Republican Club
  - Wood, Bernice
  - Wood, Francis Carter
  - Wood, J. R. Products Corp.
  - Wood, Leonard
  - Wood, Low & Co.
  - Woodall, Susie B
  - Woodard, Roy S
  - Woodbury, W B
  - Wood-hill, W
  - Woods, E
  - Woods, R McAlpine
  - Woods, S. A. Machine Co.
  - Woodson, John
  - Woodward General Hospital Fund
  - Woodward Governor Co.
  - Woodward, Roland B
  - Woodward, Roy
  - Wooliever, C E
  - Woollcott,Alexander
  - Woolsey, L H
  - Worcester, Elizabeth
  - Worcester, Fred
  - World Biographical Encyclopedia
  - World biography
  - World Federation of Education Associations
  - World Health Organization Assembly
  - World Health Organizations
  - World Neighbors
  - World Peaceways Forum
  - Wortendyke Mfg. Co.
  - WPA Adult Education Program
  - Wreden, Nicholas
  - Wright, A A
  - Wright, Elizabeth Washburn
  - Wright, J D
  - Wright, Mabel (Mrs. Edwin S)
  - Writer's War Board
  - Wu Lien Teh
  - Wunder, Mrs. Darrah Dunham
  - Wybrands, Karel
  - Wylde, Anna E
  - Wyllie, J
  - Wyman, Edgar P
  - Yalowich, Rhea S
  - Yanes, Nancy
  - Yang, Marion
  - Yeager, Clark H
  - Yohalem, A S
  - York Safe and Lock Company
  - York, Mrs. E W
  - Yost, Edna
  - Yost, Louis
  - Young Men's Christian Association
  - Young Women's Mutual Improvement Association of the Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints
  - Young, (New Delhi)
  - Young, C C
  - Young, Edward C
  - Young, Hugh H
  - Young, J P
  - Young, Nathan
  - Youngstown Sheet and Tube Co.
  - Yuen, Ruby
  - Zabriskie, Edwin G
  - Zausner Milk Company
  - Zeff, Chester M
  - Zimmerman, Jacob
  - Zimmerman, Lilly
  - Zimmerman, Minnie
  - Zurich General Accident and Liability Insurance Company Ltd.
  - Zverina, Rosamond E and Frances S
- Photographs, 25.0 Photograph(s)
  A selection of the photographs available in the Victor (Victor George) Heiser papers.
  Native American Images note: 26 black and white silver gelatin photographs of Panama, Honduras, Guatemala, and El Salvador, primarily stelae with Mayan hieroglyphics, from 1927. Photographed by Heiser on a trip to Central America in his capacity as associate director of the International Health division of the Rockefeller Foundation. Details are contained in his diary of March 31, 1927 to June 27, 1927. The photographs are housed in the photograph collection, numbers U5.4.115-139, and U5.8.80.
  - A Manobo tree house seen from the west, Philippines., 1912; F8.26.11; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of a structure built on top of a tree with people standing nearby and a fence in the foreground.
  - Aztec calendar, 1927; U5.8.80; 1.0 Photograph(s); Black and white photograph of a stone carving of the Aztec calendar, with placard, at the National Museum of Mexico.
  - Dato Mastura (left) and his judge, Dato Kali (right), full length, formal, seated., 1912; F8-26-20; 1.0 Photograph(s); Two men seated on chairs in formal full portrait.
  - Dog Market, Philippines, 1912; F8.26.15; 1.0 Photograph(s); Multiple dogs on rope leashes with unidentified people standing in background.
  - Dr. and Mrs. Victor Heiser's residence at Litchfield, Connecticut, Dr. Heiser's office., M42-24-33; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of office with desk, chair, bookshelves and large windows.
  - Drs. Heiser, Russell, and Grant of the Rockefeller Foundation negotiating a contract to build a school of public health in Tokyo., Ca. 1933; M42-24-40; 1.0 Photograph(s); Eleven people standing and sitting around a desk, with tea cups and papers.
  - Four unidentified men, full length, standing with a native hemp press, Philippines., 1912; F8-27-2; 1.0 Photograph(s); Group of people standing near and on wooden structure containing spools of hemp.
  - Group photograph of the Far Eastern Association of the Tropical Medicine. 7th. Congress, Calcutta., 1929; F11-9-5; 1.0 Photograph(s); Large group of people sitting and standing in front of a building with columns.
    Instription at bottom of photograph: "The far Eastern Association of[?] Tropical Medicine. 7th Congress, Calcutta 1929. Metchell's[?] Studio, Calcutta."
  - Group photograph of the Far Eastern Association of Tropical Medicine meeting., n. d.; F11-9-3; 1.0 Photograph(s); Group of people sitting and standing in courtyard of a building.
  - Guatemalan street scene, 1927; U5.4.128; 1.0 Photograph(s); Black and white photograph of Mayan women and children selling fruit on the curb of a city street.
  - Ifugao house, Philippines., 1912; F8-26-14; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of structure built on four tree supports with straw roof and cat in foreground.
  - Igorot boy, full length, profile, informal, seated learning the use of a typewritter at a Roman Catholic mission from Father Jurgens, full length, 3/4 profile, standing., 1912; F8-26-17; 1.0 Photograph(s); Boy sitting at desk with typewriter, out of doors with priest standing near by, trees in background.
  - Mayan carvings, 1927; U5.4.125; 1.0 Photograph(s); Black and white photograph of stone with Mayan carved figure with hieroglyphics, Central America.
  - Mayan carvings, 1927; U5.4.126; 1.0 Photograph(s); Black and white photograph of a stele containing carved Mayan hieroglyphics, Central America.
  - Panorama of a part of the town of Bontoc, Philippines., 1912; F8-26-12; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of structures in forground with mountains in background.
  - Rice terracing by the Igortes, Philippines, close up of steps., 1912; F8-26-10; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of hills and valleys cut into steps to slow erosion and aid in irrigation, close up of hill side with valley in background.
    With F8-26-9 shows rice terracing.
  - Rice terracing by the Igortes, Philippines., 1912; F8-26-9; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of hills and valley, hills having been cut into steps to aid irrigation and reduce erosion.
  - The Provincial Hospital, Philippines., 1912; F8-27-1; 1.0 Photograph(s); Two buildings with mountains in background, plants and low rock wall in foreground.
  - Unidentified woman, full length, standing wearing her typical rain coat, Philippines., 1912; F8-26-13; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length portrait of woman standing near a tree.
  - Unidentified Philippino woman and young girl, full length, 3/4 profile, informal, standing smoking cigars., 1912; 1.0 Photograph(s); Two unidentified subjects holding cigars, both with bare feet, one clothed, one nude.
  - Victor G. Heiser, half length, formal portrait., n. d.; F11-9-2; 1.0 Photograph(s); Formal portriat of Heiser, holding eye glasses and with left hand in pocket.
  - Victor George Heiser and eight unidentified men of the W. W. Keen Society of the Jefferson Medical College, five, 3/4 length, seatd and four half length, standing formal., ca. 1890; F8-27-10; 1.0 Photograph(s); Nine men sitting and standing in formal group portrait.
  - Victor George Heiser and five unidentified men, a survey group from John Hopkins University in Nashville Tenn., full length, standing., 1929, November 12; F8-27-11; 1.0 Photograph(s); Five men standing for formal group portrait.
  - Victor George Heiser with eight faculty members, standing, full length, at University of the Philippines reception, Manila., 1932, December 2; F8-25-11; 1.0 Photograph(s); Heiser in ballroom standing for formal portrait with eight unidentified people.
    Inscription on lower right corner of photograph: "Photo. F. Santos, Tel. 21054"
  - Victor George Heiser, profile, bust, informal., n. d.; F8-25-13; 1.0 Photograph(s); Profile bust of Heiser wearing glasses
  - A Bontoc Igorot man, Bontoc, Philippines., n. d.; U5-4-31; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length portrait of Bontoc Igorot man standing outside, people and plants in background.
  - Administrative building, Department of Mindanoa and Sulu, Zamboanga, P.I., September, 1914, 1914, September; U5-4-4; 1.0 Photograph(s); Exterior view of building.
  - All of the officials of the Mountain Province, Bontoc, on horse back., n. d.; U5-4-25; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of twelve men on horse back, trees and buildings in background.
  - Carabao drawn wagon, two passengers one driver., n. d.; U5-4-20; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of wagon being pulled by carabao, plants in background.
  - Company of Bontoc Igorot, Bontoc Province, Philippines., n. d.; U5-4-29; 1.0 Photograph(s); Group of soldier standing outside at attention, building in background.
  - Department Governor and Sultan of Sulu in automobile, Zamboanga, Philippines., 1914, September; U5-4-35; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of car with driver and three men, people and building in background.
  - Department Governor's Residence, Zamboanga, Philippines., n. d.; U5-4-13; 1.0 Photograph(s); Exterior view of residence, trees and stream in foreground.
  - Dinner given by Philippine Islands Medical Association in honor of past presidents, 1932., 1932, December 16; U5-3-59; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of Heiser and other men sitting at table.
  - Exterior view of building with children posing in front and in windows., U5-4-21; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of building with people lined up for photograph, hills in background.
  - Exterior view of Igorot dwelling, Bontoc Province., n. d.; U5-3-163; 1.0 Photograph(s); Exterior view of Igorot dwelling, people standing near base, trees in background.
  - Family (?) portrait, outside, Benguet Province, Philippines., n. d.; U5-4-9; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length portrait of a man, woman, and three children standing outside, hills in background.
  - Filippino orchestra., n. d.; U5-4-33; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length group portrait of men holding instruments, sitting outside.
  - Fletcher, Vezina and Forbes, of the Haitian Commission., 1930; U5-4-159; 1.0 Photograph(s); Group of men, women and children, trees in background.
    Hand written note on back of photograph: "Haiti--Hoover Commission, March 1930"
  - Forbes, White and Vezina of the Haitian Commission, standing outside, cars in background., 1930; U5.4.160; 1.0 Photograph(s); Full length view of group of men talking outside building and cars in background.
  - Four men, one seated in chair, three holding on to side, being lifted above water., n. d.; U5.4.135; 1.0 Photograph(s); View of chair being lifted above water.
    Hand written note on back of photograph: "Central America."